1 
00:00:07,600 --> 00:00:10,680
a booking chart is linked to any OpenERP model

2 
00:00:10,680 --> 00:00:13,840
this model is used for the booking chart rows

3 
00:00:16,800 --> 00:00:20,000
a resource booking is a period item displayed in the booking chart

4 
00:00:20,000 --> 00:00:23,520
the resource id make the link with the booking chart

5 
00:00:23,520 --> 00:00:26,600
origins are used to link the resource with any OpenERP object

6 
00:00:31,240 --> 00:00:33,960
the native OpenERP search widget is used 
to filter / group booking chart resources

7 
00:00:34,680 --> 00:00:37,760
when resources booking are overlapping, they are grouped

8 
00:00:38,480 --> 00:00:41,760
different dynamic zoom levels are available

9 
00:00:55,640 --> 00:00:59,080
the period navigation is made with an horizontal scrollbar

10 
00:00:59,080 --> 00:01:02,000
when the scrollbar reach one extremity, 
the next / previous month is loaded dynamically

11 
00:01:02,000 --> 00:01:05,080
and resources booking are lazy loaded

12 
00:01:18,160 --> 00:01:21,400
a click on a resource booking give access to his origin object

13 
00:01:26,040 --> 00:01:29,160
a click on a booking chart resource will display it

14 
00:01:34,000 --> 00:01:37,000
the native group feature is available

15 
00:01:45,600 --> 00:01:48,920
the calendar period is manually selectable

16 
00:01:54,400 --> 00:01:57,440
by default, the navigation is frozen 
after a manual period selection

17 
00:02:02,520 --> 00:02:05,640
the navigation can be frozen / unfrozen with a button

18 
00:02:26,360 --> 00:02:29,480
a pagination is also available on booking chart resources

